Orphan Fansubs presents
Tell me yume no tsuzuki
Tell me how the dream goes
Orphan Fansubs presents
Translation
Moho Kareshi
setsunasa wa kisetsu no sei nano
Am I sad because of the season?
Translation Check
laalg
Circuit toki no naka de
Inside the circuit of time
Timing
Yogicat
Editing & Typesetting
Collectr
kokoro ga maigo ni naru
My heart loses its way
QC
Nemesis, VigorousJammer
itsuka nante
Someday
matsu kirenakute
When I can't wait anymore
mune de hora ne
My heart pounds
sawagi dashita koukishin
With curiosity
Dive into the Cyberland
mirai no kuni he
Into the country of the future
tokimeki haneteku
I want to chase
oikaketai no
Endless excitement
meiro no saki wa
Beyond the maze
totte oki no heart beat time
The spare heart beat time
Encoding
Piyo Piyo Productions
Dive into the Cyberland
fushigi na kuni de
In a strange country
suteki ni aitai
I want a wonderful meeting
dakishimetai no
I want to embrace you
kono te ni kitto
With my hands
totte oki no heart beat time
I'll have some spare heart beat time
Tokyo, 20 Years in the Future
Captain!
There's a grenade bug?
You should've used
all your ammunition!
Too close!
T-Time out!
Alice, time out!
That's not fair, Rena.
Sorry. Dad's calling me.
I have to go.
See you at school tomorrow.
Bye-bye, Julie.
Bye-bye.
There's a grenade bug.
I'll have to tell the designer.
Rena's dad spoils her.
She's probably gonna ask him for something.
See ya.
Bye-bye. I might call you tonight.
Dad! Dad!
Dad!
Hurry, Dad.
Dad,
I love
you!
Dad, I love you!
Dad,
I love
you!
Dad, I love you!
Dad,
I love
you!
Dad, I love you!
Dad,
I love
you!
Dad, I love you!
Dad,
I love
you!
Dad, I love you!
Dad,
I love
you!
Dad...
I'm home!
Mom?
Sorry I'm late.
Welcome home, Mom.
I have intel that cyber-anarchists
in Eastern Europe are
subverting the network.
Intel, you say? We have the same information.
Are you saying the intel's false?
No. We Information Inspectors pay attention to everything.
If the cyber-anarchist really tried to crack us,
then we'd close our level 3
and higher networks.
Th-That would isolate Japan
from the rest of the world!
We'll stop them here
to prevent that from happening.
Anyway, be cautious.
Cyber-anarchists are a pain.
They don't care that in this network-connected world,
cybercrime is the most serious offense you can commit.
You have mail.
Who is it?
You are not the only one.
Lucia.
Lucia?
Who's that?
Who's Lucia?
Alice!
Cut it out! My ears are sensitive!
That sounds a little naughty!
Alice, hurry up and change,
or you'll be late.
Geez!
Now, a safety briefing about scuba diving, which is part of summer school.
Never dive alone.
Always dive with a partner.
You could die if there's no one to save you.
Oh, dear.
Yes, ma'am!
Now, Group 1, jump into the water.
Here I go!
I can't swim properly yet.
Then you should join Group 1.
But I wanna go with you, Alice.
The water's so bitter!
My eyes hurt!
Get out of the pool!
Disinfectant was released,
and there's no record of it?
Ladies, due to an accident, the school's main server has lost its data.
It will take time to repair,
so please go home early today.
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Account data at Korin Bank has been erased.
There's been a run on the bank.
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Data's been disappearing everywhere.
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
EVERYONE'S KORIN BANK
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Out of order
Sorry for the
inconvenience
Who am I?
I can't remember anything.
X CROSSING
TAXI
Idiot! Watch where you're going!
X CROSSING
TAXI
The light was red!
Yeah, sorry. I forgot how to drive.
What's with everyone?
It's like they've suddenly lost their memories.
Memories...
The Navis are spreading a virus
that erases people's memories.
Is this...
The cyber-anarchists.
One, two, one, two.
I'm home!
Excuse us.
What's that?
It's an isolation tank.
The liquid has the same mass as the human body, so I can float and relax.
Will that help you lose weight?
Oh, no! I don't need to lose
weight, right, Alice-chan?
What are you doing?
I wrote a new virus-busting program yesterday.
You're a girl. What are you doing staying up so late?
There's a virus in Cyberland that's erasing memories.
Protocol has been accepted.
This program will find
and eliminate the virus.
Wow!
File transfer!
Warning.
Are you sure you want to delete Alice's Treasure Chest?
I'm home!
She's coming home late again.
Warning.
Are you sure you want to delete Alice's Treasure Chest?
Of course not!
Reconfirmation. Are you sure you want to delete?
What's going on? I said no!
Confirmed. All memory data will be deleted in 30 seconds.
All memory data will be deleted in 20 seconds.
15.
14.
13.
What's going on?
12.
11.
Dad's... Dad's data!
10.
9.
8.
All of Dad's memories are there.
7. 6.
Who's there?
I wondered who the hacker was.
It's just a cute girl.
What a surprise.
You deserve punishment for harassing adults!
Cyber-anarchists!
That's right.
The laws of earth have no jurisdiction in Cyberland.
We're free.
I'll teach you a lesson!
If I was stronger...
Wh-What are you doing?
Are you trying to force a shutdown when I'm logging in?
What?
What's going on?
Where am I?
I called your consciousness to Cyberland, Alice.
You're not the only one, Alice.
But Dad's data was...
It's safe. Don't worry.
I have something for you.
What's this?
A program?
Wait! Let me read it!
Now you can come here whenever you want.
Cyberland is your world, Alice.
It's too fast!
Wait!
A dream?
Lucia?
Cyberland is your world, Alice.
The program?
Substitute this into the equation...
I see.
To transfer consciousness into
the virtual body, I have to change...
all the electrical potential into words.
Alice! Where are you going?
Cyberland.
Hurry.
If I don't stop the Wolf,
we'll lose all our memories.
Alice, wait up!
Five, six, seven, eight.
I'm home!
Rena, I carried the tanks
to the basement.
Why do you need them?
A diet.
Get in the tank.
Close your eyes.
Relax your body.
We'll be diving into Cyberland.
Stay together.
I feel scared.
This should be fun.
Is this all right, Lucia?
Dive in!
Their consciousness will be
forwarded to Cyberland.
Where are we?!
That's a cybergate. Be careful.
Lots of data passes through here.
Don't get swept away.
It's so strong.
Hang in there.
I see it!
This is the InterWeb!
It's the highest stratum of Cyberland, where we always exchange information.
Oh? Julie, your figure's improved.
You look really mature.
You look sexier than usual, Rena.
We probably look like our ideal selves here.
Wow.
The girls look so real!
I envy them.
I'm a cool hacker,
but I can't look like that.
Hey, isn't this level 1?
Can we go to level 3?
I don't know how far we can go,
but I trust the power Lucia gave me.
Lucia?
Yes.
This is level 2?
This is where the system administrators work.
Omata-san! Someone's
infiltrated level 2.
There are three of them.
Are they cyber-anarchists?
They've gone past level 2.
Th-This isn't good. That place...
They're headed for level 3.
It's like a grave.
It's so sad.
This is where the memory banks are.
Level 3.
Wait!
You're here.
I'm impressed you managed to dive this far.
I'll eat you!
Naughty girls won't be allowed to return to the real world.
You need to be punished.
How could you erase
our precious memories?
Rena! Touch my Navi!
Rena!
A trap?
Virus detected!
Damn it. In a place like that?
What were those three doing?
Nguyen, can't you metabolize on level 3?
The program's not ready yet.
What's going on?
How did you come this far in your human forms?
How?
If you tell me, I'll let you go.
We'd never-
Wh-What's going on?!
How?!
We have the power to destroy troublemakers in Cyberland.
Really?
What?!
Can I trust you, Lucia?
Alice, protect Cyberland.
Disinfection sword!
If you don't exit soon, you won't be able to leave this place.
You're sure about that, little girl?
You'll never be able
to enter Cyberland again!
You've humiliated the cyber-anarchists!
Prepare yourselves!
You were so cool, Alice!
I could've beaten it
with my bare hands.
Time for us to exit.
An anonymous helper solved the memory bank erasures,
Terrorist
Acts Have
Ended
which were of unknown origin.
Every memory bank has been repaired.
Terrorist
Acts Have
Ended
Terrorist
Acts Have
Ended
The Bureau of Information has announced that it is investigating the situation.
Someone saved Cyberland.
That much is certain.
But who?
Liar!
I can wear a sexy swimsuit too!
No, you can't!
You need to go on a diet before next summer.
The signal's green.
Wait!
Say sayonara iu kawari ni hohoende
Don't say goodbye, smile instead
ja mata ne to te wo furitai
I'll see you again. I'll wave my hand
Now hitomi wo hora tojitara omoide no
Now I close my eyes and remember
Scene parade no you ni flashback
Scene: a flashback like a parade
oboete ite sou yuuki dashite
I remember it, and I feel brave
arukidashita saisho no atsui kaze
I feel a hot breeze as I walk
kimi ni aete yokatta
I'm glad I met you
yuuhi ni ima naranda
We're lined up in front of the sunset
Silhouette hanareteiku keredo nakanai
Your silhouette disappears, but I won't cry
honto ni tanoshikatta
I had a lot of fun
mune de sotto chikatta
I swore to my heart
mata aeru yakusoku shinakutemo
That we can meet again. I don't need to promise
Never end kisetsu sugitemo
It will never end, even after the season
Never cry hanarete itemo
I'll never cry, even if we're separated
Don't forget issho ni sugoshita toki wo wasurenai
Don't forget the time we spent together
See you next time.
I'm Minazuki Alice.
I'm tired of fighting those disgusting monsters to protect Cyberland.
We met Charlie in Cyberland. Julie fell in love with him,
but someone's trying to kill him.
Julie said she'd protect him, but she seems to have her own reasons.
Alice in Cyberland, episode two:
Crisis in Cyberland!
Dive in!
Alice in Cyberland
Crisis in Cyberland
On sale Feb 25, 1997
Alice in Cyberland
Game Visual Collection